anime.place 2016-05-06

# Privacy Policy « The Anime Place – Watch English Dubbed and Subbed Anime Episodes Online

____Pages __Privacy Policy

This privacy policy sets out how The Anime Place uses and protects any information that you give knowingly or unknowingly to The Anime Place when you use this website. The Anime Place is committed to your privacy, any information collected is neither sold nor freely given to third parties except where stated in this privacy policy.

The Anime Place may, from time to time, change this privacy policy. As a guest of this website, you should check this page to see if any changes were made. The changes were last made on  **June 21st, 2015 – Father’s Day.**

## Information We Directly Collect

*         Optional  
**       Optional, however IP Information may give this detail away on it’s own.  
***     Required, User can avoid giving this information by not signing up for the website.  
****   Automatically Obtained, Can’t be opted out of.

### Via the Forum

Time Zone Details**

Birthday*

AIM Account*

MSN Account*

ICQ Account*

Yahoo Account*

Jabber Account*

Skype Account*

Personal Website URL*

Gender*

Location**

Interests*

E-mail***

IP****

### Via the website

E-mail***

IP****

IP Address information is automatically obtained anytime the user connects to the website, this cannot be prevented. User profiles can, on request, be deleted. We may require additional validation when a user wishes to delete their profile which will delete all other information that we collect, excluding IP Addresses and information that can be extrapolated from that IP Address.

**Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements**  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.  
Requests to delete an account can be e-mailed to support@anime.place or requested via a message posted on the forums.

## Information that is collected by third parties.

The Anime Place uses a chat service called “Chatango”. Their policy is located [at this link](https://chatango.com/page?full_privacy).

The Anime Place uses an analytical service called “Google Analytics”, The Google privacy policy is located [at this link](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/).

The Anime Place utilizes advertising services from [AdsOptimal](https://www.adsoptimal.com/tos/privacy), [CPMStar](https://www.cpmstar.com/privacyPolicy.html), [EvolveNation](http://www.evolvenation.com/privacy_policy) and [PlaywireMedia](http://playwiremedia.com/privacy/). Click on the name of the advertising service to be directed to their privacy policy.

The Anime Place utilizes a video player known as JW Player that has analytical services. The video player’s privacy policy is located [at this link](http://www.jwplayer.com/privacy/).

The Anime Place uses a DNS and DDoS Protection service known as Cloudflare. Here is it’s [privacy policy](https://www.cloudflare.com/security-policy).

The Anime Place uses a sharing service called AddThis which allows you to share The Anime Place with your friends at the click of a button. Here is it’s [privacy policy](http://www.addthis.com/privacy/privacy-policy).

The Anime Place uses facebook. The embedded widget may indirectly collect information about your activities. Here is the facebook [privacy policy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy).
